苏菲
Sophie!
苏菲  你在里面吗
Sophie, are you in there?
苏菲  还有15分钟就队伍就要出发了
Sophie, the procession starts in 15 minutes.
如果那个女孩毁了你的婚礼
If that girl ruins your wedding--
我不是担心婚礼  妈妈
I'm not worried about the wedding, mother.
我担心苏菲
I'm worried about Sophie.
若昨晚我也像她那样喝那么多香槟
If I had as much champagne as she did last night,
我铁定要迟到
I'd probably be late for February.
能帮忙打开这门吗  很紧急
Can you open this door for us? It's an emergency. Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
苏菲
Sophie.
床没动过
The bed hasn't been slept in.
也不在洗手间
She's not in the bathroom.
看她的礼服还在不在
Go and see if her dress is still here.
绑结实点儿
Make sure it's nice and tight.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
你们这是在干什么
What on earth are you two doing?
做研究
Research.
老爸在下一章里写道  妮基·希特
Dad has Nikki Heat duct-taped to a chair
被胶带绑在了椅子上
in his next chapter,
他不知道该怎样让她逃脱
and he doesn't know how to get her out of it.
我想  最好的办法
I thought, what better way to figure it out
莫过于从她的角度来思考
than to get into the mind of my character.
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得你完全可以凭想象力
I suppose you could just use your imagination.
我希望写逼真一点  还有手
Well, I want it to be authentic. Hands.
赶紧绑好你爸爸
Well, hurry taping up your father.
我们可不能迟到了
We don't want to be late.
完了  说漏嘴了
Oh, God. I can't believe I just said that.
你们要去干嘛
Where are you two off to?
奶奶要参加彩排  我想去看
Gram's got a dress rehearsal. I thought I'd go watch.
是看我
Watch me
还是第二场那个送外卖的帅小伙
or watch the adorable delivery boy in the second act?
紧不紧
Too tight?
非常好
Perfect.
你确定要把嘴封上吗
And you're sure about your mouth?
我说过了  要逼真
Like I said, authentic.
可以就点头
Nod if you're okay.
好  出发  完事后可能会去购物
Okay. We're off, and after, we might go shopping.
所以
So...
你不介意  对吧
You don't mind, right?
别这样  老爸
Oh, come on, dad.
要是我不拿  你就不关心我了
We both know you'd have no respect for me if I didn't.
玩得愉快  祝你好运
Have fun and good luck.
我不知道她从哪儿学的  真不知道
I don't know where she gets it from. Honestly, I don't.
-再见  -再见
- Bye  - Adios.
死者是苏菲·朗森  35岁
Victim is Sophie Ronson, 35.
从洛杉矶来参加婚礼
She's in from LA for the wedding.
是客人吗
Was she a guest?
不是  伴娘
Mnh-mnh. Bridesmaid.
朗森小姐没去做妆发
The bride came looking
新娘就过来查看
when Ms. Ronson didn't show up for her hair and makeup.
结果在大衣橱里发现了她
Found her stuffed in that armoire.
有什么发现
What do you see?
初步分析死者为窒息而死
Preliminary cause is asphyxiation.
从气管的扭曲形状来看
And from the way her windpipe is crushed,
凶手是从死者身后行凶
I'd say the killer choked her from behind.
咽喉处有挫伤
We've got contusions on her throat,
一只耳环不见踪影
one of her earrings is missing.
像是被从耳垂扯下
It looks like it was yanked from her lobe.
搜遍了房间  也没发现耳环
We searched the room. The earring's not here.
通知鉴证组  打印出耳环的照片
Get CSU to print out a picture
这样同事可在整个酒店范围搜寻
so that uniforms can start searching the hotel.
好的
Yeah.
死亡时间
Time of death?
从室温和尸斑来看
Based on temperature and lividity,
我估计是凌晨三点到五点之间
I'd say between 3:00 and 5:00 am this morning.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - Hmm.
去和酒店保安人员谈谈
Let's talk to hotel security.
我要看监视录像
I want to see surveillance tapes
所有登记入住的客人名单
and a list of all registered hotel guests.
死者手机及房间电话的通话记录
And get records for her room phone and her cell.
马上去办
I'm on it.
酒店方面说只给了死者一张房卡
Hotel says only one key card was issued to the victim.
这张卡最后一次使用是在凌晨3点18分
It was last used to enter the victim's room at 3:18 am.
和死亡时间吻合
Okay, well, that coincides with time of death.
新娘和新郎在哪儿
Where are the bride and groom?
婚礼套房  在大厅尽头
Bridal suite at the end of the hall.
叫格雷格和凯拉
Uh, Greg And Kyra.
让同事召集参加婚礼的所有客人
Okay, have uniforms assemble the wedding guests
到酒吧间  接受询问
in the bar to be interviewed.
卡塞尔在哪儿
Where's Castle?
不知道  调查伴娘的死因
I don't know. Figured the death of a bridesmaid
正适合他干
would be right up his alley.
他可能听到"婚礼" 就临阵退缩了
He heard "wedding" and probably got cold feet?
最后见到苏菲是什么时候
When was the last time that you saw Sophie?
在昨晚的预演晚宴上
At the rehearsal dinner last night.
我好像都没跟她说话
I don't even think I talked to her.
她为了我们  一路赶过来
She came all this way for us,
我甚至都没跟她打招呼
and I don't think I even said hello.
这不是你的错  凯拉  昨天太忙乱了
It's not your fault, Kyra. It was a crazy day.
我去睡觉后  你们聊过吗
Did you talk to her after I went up to bed?
没有  你知道泰迪叔叔这个人的
No. You know how uncle Teddy is.
在没喝倒之前他是不会放我走的
He wouldn't let me leave without doing tequila shots.
大约1点的时候  我溜回了房间
I escaped up to my room around 1:00.
我不知道苏菲是否还在酒吧间
I'm not sure if Sophie was still at the bar.
昨晚你们不在同一间房吗
The two of you weren't in the same room last night?
不在
No.
婚礼前见新娘会带来霉运
It's bad luck to see the bride before the wedding.
关于苏菲  我还有些问题
Is there anything else you can tell me about Sophie?
她是否在恋爱  有没有仇人
Was she in a relationship? Did she have any enemies?
我不清楚
I don't know.
她在洛杉矶  我们并不是十分亲密
She lived in LA, and we-- we were never super close.
是苏菲介绍我们认识的
Sophie introduced us.
因为她  我们才能在一起
She's the reason we're together.
所以我们准备婚礼的时候
So when we were planning the wedding,
就想到应该把她请来
we thought she should be there.
好几年了  订婚晚宴才第一次见到她
But the engagement party was the first time we'd seen her
而她现在却死了
in a couple of years, and now she's dead.
谁会做这样的事呢
Who would do something like this?
我们会查出来的
That's what we're here to find out.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢  乔  太好了
Thanks, Joe. That's great.
酒店安保部门吗
Hotel security?
是的  他们调查了所有员工的信息
Yeah. They do background checks on all their employees.
很确定凶手不在其中
Seemed pretty sure there wasn't a killer among them,
不过还是给了我名单
but he gave me the list.
还在调监控录像
He's also pulling the surveillance tapes.
好消息是  电梯的摄像头都在运作
Good news is, the elevators are all wired. Bad news is,
坏消息是楼梯和走廊的没有
the stairwells and hallways aren't.
看这是谁呀
Oh, look who it is.
我们正准备派搜索队呢  你到哪儿去了
We were about to send out a search party. Where you been?
我在忙着写小说
Uh, I got a little tied up with work.
-犯罪现场在哪儿  -六楼
- Which way to the crime scene?  - Sixth floor.
-谢谢  -不客气  喂
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm. Hey.
兄弟  你裤子上的是胶带吗
Bro... is that duct tape on your pants?
是的  是的  没错
Yes. Yes, it is.
死者是伴娘
So a bridesmaid, huh?
怎么回事
What happened?
不会是穿着礼服被杀害的吧
Wouldn't get caught dead in that dress?
其实也没那么差劲
They're actually not that bad.
是条淡紫色的雪纺纱裙
A subtle mauve chiffon.
兄弟  真的吗  淡紫色的
Dude, really? Mauve?
怎么啦  我有姐妹的
What? I have sisters.
你该看看她们的礼服  奇丑无比
You should've seen their dresses--hideous.
伴娘的礼服本来就该丑一些
Ah, bridesmaid dresses are supposed to be hideous.
是吗  为什么
Really, why?
那样的话  对比起来新娘就漂亮多啦
So that the bride looks more beautiful in comparison.
看到没
Ah, see?
每个女人都会想象她的婚礼
Not a woman alive who doesn't think about her wedding day,
连凯特·贝克特也不例外
not even Kate Beckett.
别告诉我  你从没从杂志上剪下
Tell me you never tore a picture of a wedding gown
中意的婚纱
out of a magazine.
我从没从杂志上剪过婚纱
I've never torn a picture of a wedding gown out of a magazine.
你撒谎
You're lying.
-她在撒谎  -赞成
- She's lying. - Mm-hmm.
倒霉的新娘是哪位
So who's the unlucky bride?
她叫
Uh, her name is...
凯拉
Kyra?
里克
Rick?
里克·卡塞尔
Rick Castle.
你们认识
You two know each other?
可不仅仅是认识
That would be an understatement.
我看到报道说  你跟着警方做事
I read somewhere that you were working with the police,
但做梦也想不到
But I-I never would've expected to...
多久没见了
How long has it been?
-太久了  -你一点都没变
- Too long. - You look exactly the same.
你变漂亮了
And you've improved.
你总是很会说话
You always did know how to turn a phrase.
这真是
This is...
太像做梦了
So surreal.
今天是我结婚的日子
It's my wedding day,
而你却出现了
and you...show up.
卡塞尔  蕾妮有新发现
Castle, Lanie's got something for us.
我会过去的
I'll catch up.
行  好吧
Hmm. Okay.
发现了什么
What'd you find?
我把死者翻过来时
Once I turned her over,
看到了她背部上方的这些擦伤
I saw these abrasions across her upper back.
肯定是死前造成的
They were definitely made before she died,
可能是在挣扎的过程中造成的
probably during the struggle.
是什么造成的呢
Any idea what made them?
不知道  不过伤痕的形状很奇怪
No, but there's an odd shape to the wounds.
回到实验室就能知道了
I'll have a better idea once I get her back to the lab.
好的
Okay.
婚礼套房情况如何
So how's everything going in the bridal suite?
没有如期举行婚礼
Not the day they had planned.
是啊  不过有神秘嘉宾
Yeah, or the surprise guest.
显然卡塞尔和新娘之间有段历史
Apparently Castle has a history with the bride.
古代史  现代史  还是爱情史
Ancient, modern or sexual?
看起来都有
Seems like all of the above.
你不介意吗
You're okay with that?
不介意啊  我为什么要介意
Yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
有消息随时告诉我
Just keep me posted on the labs.
那个说过婚姻制度
So what happened to the girl
属于侏罗纪的女孩怎么结婚了
who said that marriage was a Jurassic institution?
她长大了
She grew up.
那是不是也意味着新郎也是个成年人
Mm. Does that mean the groom is a grown-up, too?
成天工作不休息
All work and no play.
不是  他适当休息
No. He plays just enough.
他真幸运
He's a lucky man.
除了今天
Except today.
那些担心
All the things
会在婚礼上出错的事
you worry about going wrong at your wedding...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
格雷格
Greg.
-这是里克·卡塞尔  -里克·卡塞尔
- This is Rick Castle. - Rick Castle.
你的前男友
Your ex.
是  不是  很高兴见到你
Oh, yes. No-- it's nice to meet you.
里克现在和警察一起工作
Rick's working with the police now.
他们认为凶手还在酒店里吗
Do they think the murderer is still in the hotel?
那得看这次事件是意外
Well, that depends on whether the attack was random
还是熟人所为
or someone she knew.
你认为凶手可能在客人当中
So you think one of the guests could've killed her?
警方必须考虑各种可能性
We have to consider every possibility.
抱歉我们得先离开下
You'll have to excuse us.
-楼下有客人  -当然
- We have people arriving downstairs. - Of course.
凯拉·布莱恩
Kyra Blaine.
我猜她对你而言很特别
I take it she was someone very special.
她是那个离开的人
She's the one that got away.
能告诉我姓名
Could you please tell me your name
以及跟新郎新娘的关系吗
and relationship to the bride and groom?
希拉·布莱恩  新娘的母亲
Sheila Blaine, mother of the bride.
吉斯·墨菲  新郎的兄弟
Keith Murphy. I'm the brother of the groom.
劳里·希尔  伴娘  新娘的朋友
Laurie Hill, maid of honor, friend of the bride.
泰迪·墨菲  新郎的叔叔
Ted Murphy, groom's uncle.
鲁比·奥西里斯·斯瓦兹曼
Ruby Osiris-Schwartzman.
曾嫁给和凯拉父亲的兄弟
I was once married to Kyra's father's
有共同曾祖的叔叔
brother's uncle twice removed.
不该嫁他的  酒吧间营业了吗
And, boy, was that a mistake. Is the bar open yet?
你觉得谁有可能是凶手
Do you have any idea who might have killed her?
当然不知道
Of course not.
不知道
No.
我听说苏菲根本不打算来
I heard that Sophie almost didn't come to the wedding.
她给凯拉打电话  试图推掉
She called Kyra up and tried to back out
做伴娘的任务
of being a bridesmaid.
但后来又打来说改变了主意
But then she called and said she changed her mind.
我警告过凯拉
I warned Kyra.
邀请她当伴娘根本靠不住
That girl was too unreliable to be put in a wedding party.
但她不听老人言  吃亏了
But did she listen to me? No.
非常感谢你  下一位
Thank you very much. Next!
所有人都问过了  对吗
That's everyone, right?
差不多都在这
I think so.
等等  这个伴郎没划掉
Wait. There's a groomsman that's not checked off.
麦克·怀特
Mike Weitz.
我没跟他谈过  你呢
Hmm. I didn't talk to him. You?
也没有
No.
墨菲先生
Mr. Murphy.
你看见麦克·怀特了吗
Have you seen Mike Weitz?
事实上  没有
No, actually.
有人看到过麦克吗
Has anybody seen Mike?
天  预演晚宴时他和苏菲在一起
Oh, God. He was with Sophie at the rehearsal dinner.
对  之后还在酒吧看见他们一起
She's right. I saw them together in the bar after.
你不会是觉得他也出事了吧
You don't think something happened to him, too, do you?
昨晚之后就没有客人见到过麦克
None of the guests have seen Mike since last night.
搜过房间  床没动过
We checked his room. The bed's made.
燕尾服还挂在衣橱里
His tux is still hanging in the closet.
房卡记录显示最后一次开门是凌晨2点
And his key card shows his last entry at 2:00 am.
凌晨2点  有什么异常吗
2:00 am. All right. Any signs of foul play?
没有  他的牙刷跟行李都在房间
No, but his toothbrush and bags are still there.
让酒店安保部门搜查整座酒店
Have hotel security start searching the premises.
你觉得他也遇害了吗
You think we're gonna find another body?
麦克是凶手的可能性更大
More likely, Mike's our killer,
他勒死苏菲  跑路了
And he ran off after strangling Sophie.
发布通缉令
So put an A.P.B. out.
把麦克的照片发到机场和火车站
Get Mike's photos to all airports and train stations.
我去找参加婚礼的客人  看是否能
I'll check back with the wedding guests, see if I can
找到麦克跟苏菲交谈的清晰照片
get a clear picture of Mike and Sophie's interactions.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
或者我们自己就可以看看
Or...we could watch last night's festivities
昨晚的欢宴
for ourselves...
小巧的数码相机里应该就有
on these handy-dandy digital video cameras.
我们当时都在逃命呢
There we are, running for our lives, right...
麦克在做演讲
That's Mike giving a speech.
苏菲的目光转向麦克
and that's sophie looking away from us.
歪歪倒倒走过走廊
Serpentined down the hallway.
就在那时  吉斯决定
And that's when-- that's when Keith decides...
得慢点走
he's gonna slow him down a little bit.
他拿起一个灭火器
So he grabs a fire extinguisher...
-谁在别人演讲时接电话呢  -就是 没礼貌
- Who takes a call during a speech? - Right? Rude.
他喊道  我看不见  我看不见啦
And he's yelling, "I can't see! I can't see!"
她是跟谁通话呢
Wonder who she's talking to?
暂停
Pause that.
这不是很奇怪吗   麦克演讲的中途
Does anyone else find it odd that Sophie would leave
苏菲就离开了
in the middle of Mike's speech?
也许打电话的人想要见她呢
Maybe whoever called wanted to meet.
但会是谁呢
Yeah, but who?
参加预演晚宴的人都在那里
Everyone at the rehearsal dinner is sitting in that room.
按照显示的时间
Well, according to the time code,
查查这个在7点41打进来的号码
that call came in at about 7:41.
苏菲手机的通话记录显示这个电话来自
Sophie's cell phone history shows the call came from...
酒店大堂
the hotel lobby.
跟酒店方核实下
Check with the hotel.
看他们是否有摄像头
See if they have any security cameras
覆盖公用电话区域
covering the phones.
好极了  谢谢
That's perfect. Thanks.
等等  我知道他是谁
Wait a minute. I know this guy.
嘉伯
Uh, Gamble.
-博伊德·嘉伯  -他是毒贩吗
- Boyd Gamble. - So he's a dealer?
当初基本是卖大麻和可卡因
Mostly weed and coke back in the day.
干了不少年  后来有毒贩想霸占他的地盘
Did a couple of years for assaulting another drug dealer
就海扁了对方
who was trying to muscle in on his turf.
把那人揍了个半死
Beat him up real bad, too.
听起来他脾气火爆啊
Sounds like he's got a bad temper.
也许现在升级到杀人了
Maybe he's graduated to murder.
好极了  带他来
Great. Go pick him up.
是关于麦克的吗
Was that about Mike?
不是  只是跟进线索
Uh, no. Just following up on a lead.
你的礼服很漂亮
Your dress is lovely, by the way.
非常感谢
Oh, thank you so much.
你叫凯特对吗
It--it's Kate, right?
是的
Yeah.
我从《妮基·希特》的致谢里
I feel like I know you a little...
看到你的名字
from Nikki Heat, the dedication.
里克写的书我都看
I still read all of Rick's books.
卡塞尔的书都只是他
Yeah, well, most of that book is just a result
胡思乱想的结果
of Castle's overactive imagination.
你这么称呼他真有意思
It's funny that you call him that.
卡塞尔
Castle.
我认识的他  只是里克
When I knew him, he was just Rick,
写的书刚开始畅销
fresh off his first best seller.
不管是否是胡思乱想
Well, overactive imagination or not,
我清楚他在书里的致谢
I know he only dedicates his books...
只为他真正在乎的人
to people he really cares for.
杀人
Murder?
你们傻了啊
What, are you nuts?
我们知道你在酒店见过苏菲
We know you met Sophie at the hotel, Boyd.
几个钟头后  她就死了
A couple hours later, she turns up dead.
你不该给个交待吗
You want to tell us how that happened?
我们在公园见的面
She met me in the park.
我有个熟人跟她推荐来我这买货
We had a mutual acquaintance who recommended my services.
她知道她要什么我都能给
She knew I could get her what she needed.
为什么卖了毒品还不放手
Why didn't you just sell her the drugs and be done with it?
怎么还去了酒店
Why did you show up at the hotel?
因为她要的东西很特别
Because she needed a specialty item.
当时我身上没货  说好拿到货就打给她
I didn't have any on me, so I told her I'd call her when I did.
什么特别的货
What specialty item?
氟硝西泮
Flunitrazepam.
迷药
Roofies?
伴娘要迷药做什么
Why would a bridesmaid need roofies?
想占帅哥的便宜
You want to take advantage of a guy,
迷晕他基本就无法实现目的了
knocking him unconscious kind of defeats the purpose.
最佳方案  说句话就成
The best way--just ask.
我会帮你办好的
I'll take care of it for you.
你好  希拉
Hello, Sheila.
理查德
Richard.
我想你正是这场混乱的罪魁祸首
Figures you'd be at the heart of this mess.
贝克特探长  这位是希拉·布莱恩
Detective Beckett, this is Sheila Blaine,
新娘的母亲
mother of the bride.
最后我竟然没有无家可归
So I guess I didn't end up homeless or teaching
也没在新罕布什尔州的三流大学教书
at a third-rate college in New Hampshire after all.
一切还有待时间去验证
There's still time.
我总会想起我们的特别谈话
I've missed our special talks.
希拉不喜欢搞艺术的穷小子
Sheila didn't approve of struggling artists.
你肯定大爱格雷格吧  他家有钱吧
You must like Greg, though. He's from money, right?
理查德  其实从来和钱无关
It was never about the money, Richard.
只有关优点
It was about character.
如果你有优点的话  早就知道这点了
And you would know that if you had any.
厉害
Wow.
想象下  如果你们没分手
Just imagine-- if things had worked out...
你得和她一起过感恩节了
you'd be spending thanksgivings with her.
贝克特  好  很好
Beckett. Okay, great.
找到麦克了
They think they found Mike.
救命啊
Help!
有人吗  救命
Anybody! Help!
怀特先生  麦克
Mr. Weitz? Mike.
苏菲那个臭女人呢  我要杀了她
Where's that bitch Sophie? I'll kill her.
时间  完全不对
Timing--very poor.
怎么了
What happened?
那个女人给我下了药
That little freak drugged me.
那么  麦克
All right, Mike.
说说昨晚和苏菲之间发生了什么
Walk me through what happened with you and Sophie last night.
她勾引的我
Mm. She came on to me is what happened.
跟我调情  还给了我杯酒
Acted all flirty, brought me a drink.
下了迷药的酒
A drink spiked with roofies.
神经吧
Yeah, nuts, right?
谁会给男人下药  女人说一句话就行
I mean, who roofies a guy? All a girl has to do is ask.
就是
Mm.
你们俩在一起过吗
Did the two of you have history?
没有  我们去年
No. I mean, I-I saw her last year
在格雷格和凯拉订婚派对上见过
at Greg and Kyra's engagement party.
男人看见她  都会移不开目光的
She was definitely the kind of girl you noticed.
不过说实话  我们没说过几句话
But, uh, no, I-I don't think we so much as even talked.
知道她为什么要对你下药吗
Any idea why she'd want to drug you?
不知道
No clue.
她的样子有没有生气或是紧张恐惧
Did she seem angry, nervous or scared?
没有  她像是心意已定
No. She seemed... determined.
我早该知道馅饼砸不中我的
Guess I should've known it was too good to be true, huh?
如果想到什么  请通知警方
If you can think of anything else, let us know.
好的
Okay.
苏菲昨晚到底意欲何为
What was Sophie up to last night?
她中途出去拿迷药
She went out of her way to get those drugs.
肯定早有预谋
She definitely had a plan.
迷晕麦克  把他关在衣橱里
To roofie Mike and lock him in a closet?
到底是什么诡异计划呢
What kind of a bizarre plan is that?
也许
Maybe...
我也不知道
No, I got nothing.
兄弟  吃的  快吃  饿死了
Oh, dude. Catering. Grab it. Oh, I'm so hungry.
那是什么  谢谢
What is that? Thanks.
你们在干嘛
What are you guys doing?
饿了一整天了
Haven't eaten all day.
土豆饼真是太赞了
These potato pancakes are incredible.
还有一点也很赞的
You know what else is incredible? Hmm?
一旦开始调查死者的私生活
How much information we're gonna find
拿到的信息量也很赞
once we start investigating our victim's life.
自苏菲·朗森的飞机抵达纽约
I want to know everything about Sophie Ronson
直到她死亡前的每一件事
from the moment that her plane landed in New York
都要查的清清楚楚
to the moment she was found dead--
跟谁通电话  做了什么  在哪里吃饭
Who she called, what she did and where she ate.
我是凯特·贝克特探长
This is Detective Kate Beckett.
要一张搜查令  查苏菲·朗森的财务状况
I need a warrant on financials for a Sophie Ronson.
-我是莱恩  -你好  萨拉
- Yeah, it's Ryan. - Hey, Sarah.
你去查查出租车调度情况
Yeah. Yeah, I need you to reach out to all the taxi dispatchers...
帮个忙  我要苏菲·朗森的手机通讯记录
Do me a favor. I need the cell records on Sophie Ronson.
一小时后要  好
Uh, in about an hour. All right.
实在舍不得浪费
Couldn't let it go to waste.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我就是想了想  什么地方
I just figured, what was the one place
会没人去找你
where no one would think to look for you?
举行婚礼的地方
At a wedding.
为你举行婚礼的地方
At your wedding.
格雷格在哪呢
Where's... Greg.
-是  -他忙着应对全局呢
- Right. - He's taking care of things.
那是他擅长的
He's good at that.
所以  要是你不结婚
So if you don't get married,
这不过是块普通蛋糕了
is it just a regular old cake?
这个还是结婚蛋糕
It's still wedding cake.
多层蛋糕  插花  摆在舞会大厅
It's tiered, cut flowers, it's in a ballroom.
如果今天一切按计划走
If things had gone as planned today,
此时此刻  我应该
I would be twirling around
手携夫君翩翩起舞
on the dance floor with my husband right about now.
还记得我们最后一次跳舞吗
Do you remember the last time we danced?
在中央车站的大钟下面
Under the clock at Grand Central Station.
你去肯尼迪机场赶一趟飞伦敦的航班
You were on your way to JFK to catch a flight to London.
你本该也跟着去的
You were supposed to follow me.
但你说你需要空间
You said you needed space.
可我没说需要无限的空间
I didn't mean forever.
反正婚礼你都经历过了
So you've done all of this before.
两次了
Twice.
当时  你总认为那个她是真爱吗
And each time, did you think that she was the one?
当时看来  结婚是正确的选择
It seemed like the right thing to do at the time.
可事实上并非如此  对吗
But it wasn't, was it?
有女孩会认为今天的事是个预兆
Some girls would think what happened today is a sign.
你是说谋杀案
The murder?
还有你的出现
And you.
卡塞尔
Castle.
我们准备走了  你要搭便车吗
We're on our way. I thought you might need a ride.
我要上楼了
I should go upstairs.
大家可能会找我
They'll be looking for me.
来点蛋糕吗
Cake?
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
我们是在大学里认识的
We met in college.
在一起差不多三年
We were together nearly three years.
我又没有问
I didn't ask.
但是你心中充满问号
Yes, you were not asking very loudly.
她和你的两位前妻可不一样
She's different from your ex-wives.
怎么说
What do you mean?
她是踏实过日子的
She's real.
我并不觉得你喜欢这种类型
I didn't think you went for real.
分手让你很痛苦吧
Tough breakup?
很久以前的事了
It was a long time ago.
-你打电话给我了  -是的
- You called? - Yes.
在死者背部的伤痕发现微量金属
I found traces of metal in the abrasions on Sophie's back.
-是什么金属  -我也不清楚
- What kind of metal? - I have no idea.
不过已经把样本送去联调局实验室了
But I sent a sample over to the FBI lab
看他们是否能缩小化学特性范围
to see if they can narrow down the chemical signature.
明天应该会有结果
We should have the results tomorrow.
如果找到造成伤痕的凶器
If I find the object that made the wounds,
可以证明其吻合吗
you'll be able to match it?
没问题
Absolutely.
太好了  还有别的吗
Great. Anything else?
看你是否坦白了
You tell me.
坦白什么
What?
别卖关子了  卡塞尔的旧情人
Don't "what" me. Castle's lost love.
你在说什么
Yeah. What about it?
还跟姐姐装蒜是吧
Girl, I'm gonna smack you.
你们每天形影不离地工作
You work side by side every day.
他以你为蓝本在书中大写性爱场景
He writes a sex scene in his book about you
看得我都要喝冰水降温
that had me reaching for ice water.
现在半路杀出来一个新娘旧情人
Now little Miss Bride shows up,
别告诉我你一点酸劲儿都没有
don't tell me you're not the least bit jealous.
得了吧
Oh, please.
我看你在这里药水味闻太多了
You have been inhaling too many autopsy fluids.
亲爱的  不识庐山真面目
Honey, just because you can't see what's going on
只缘身在此山中
doesn't mean everyone else doesn't see what's going on.
闭嘴
Shut up.
呵呵  我可是清楚的很
Mm-hmm. Cause I see it.
你看不见了  但是我可以
You may not, but I do.
这段床上戏写得好详细啊
There's a lot of detail in this love scene.
你们不是应该在做背景调查吗
Aren't you guys supposed to be running background checks?
我们正在调查新娘的背景
We are. On the bride.
昨天一整天  我都觉得
All day yesterday, I kept feeling like
凯拉·布莱恩这个名字似曾相识
I'd heard the name Kyra Blaine before.
果然想起  就在卡塞尔第二本书的致谢里
And then it hits me the dedication of Castle's second book.
《永不凋零的玫瑰》
"A Rose for Everafter."
谨以此献给凯拉·布莱恩  星月因你无光
"For Kyra Blaine, you make the stars shine."
我不在  你们是不是互相编辫子玩儿
When I'm not here, do you guys braid each other's hair
还讨论乔纳斯兄弟[偶像乐队]中哪个最酷
and debate who's the coolest Jonas Brother?
没有  但既然你提起了  当然是尼克
No, but it's totally Nick.
-绝对是尼克最酷  -没错  凯文是最有才的一个
- Absolutely Nick. - Yep. Kevin's the talented one.
尼克真可爱  乔呢
Yeah, Nick's the cute one. Joe?
房卡
The key card.
迈克的房卡
Mike's key card!
酒店记录显示昨天凌晨2点
Hotel records indicate that Mike's key card locks access of hotel room
迈克的房卡被用过
at 2:00 am yesterday morning.
当时他正在储藏间里人事不省
Only he was busy passed out in a supply closet
胃里全是迷药
with a bellyful of roofies.
那究竟是谁进了迈克的房间
So who swiped into Mike's room?
迈克说他醒来时就发现门卡不见了
Mike said his key card was missing when he woke up.
很明显被苏菲偷了  但她为什么这么做
Well, Sophie must have stolen it. But why?
谢谢
Thank you.
迈克失踪时
Didn't uniforms already search this room
警队不是搜过这个房间了吗
when he went missing?
是  迈克说没发现有什么不对劲的
Yeah. Mike said he didn't notice anything out of place.
这房间到底有什么猫腻
So what could be so important in this room
要大费周章地对一个男人下药
it'd be worth the trouble of drugging a man?
也许这间房不是苏菲的目标
Maybe it wasn't this room she was trying to get in to.
打开隔壁房门的唯一原因就是
The only reason to unlock the door adjacent to yours is if...
知道你的芳邻是谁
You knew who your neighbor was.
苏菲进迈克房间的原因可能是
Maybe Sophie only wanted to get in to Mike's room
为了来这个房间
so she could get in to this one.
这是谁的房间
So whose room is this?
卡塞尔
Castle.
苏菲那只失了踪的耳环
Sophie's missing earring.
她可能是在此遇害的
This could be where she was killed.
你们在我房间做什么
Hey, what are you doing in my room?
这太离谱了  我没有杀苏菲·朗森
This is crazy. I did not kill Sophie Ronson.
那怎么在你的房间找到了她的耳环
Then how did her earring end up in your room?
你现在有机会澄清这一切  格雷格
You have a chance to come clean here, Greg.
如果我是你  我会讲实话
If I were you, I would take it.
我大概凌晨一点回到房间
I got back to the room around 1:00.
当时烂醉如泥
I was pretty drunk.
稍有意识已是凌晨两点
Next thing I know it was 2:00 in the morning,
有人在我的床上
and somebody was in bed with me,
对我上下其手
and they had their hands down my pants.
我以为是凯拉  以为她改变主意了
I thought it was Kyra. I-I-I figured she changed her mind
关于婚礼前分房睡...
about spending the night apart.
但居然是苏菲
But it wasn't. It was Sophie.
于是你想  管他的  见谁上谁
And you figured, what the hell? Love the one you're with.
不
No.
少装了  格雷格  苏菲很漂亮
Oh, come on, Greg. Sophie's a beautiful girl,
而且你只有数小时的自由了
and you were hours away from
马上就要戴上婚姻的枷锁
strapping on the ball and chain for life.
我爱凯拉  我永远不会背叛她
No. I love Kyra. I would never cheat on her,
尤其不会因为苏菲而背叛她
especially with Sophie.
为什么尤其不会因为苏菲
Why especially with Sophie?
你以前和苏菲上过床吗
Had you slept with her before?
为什么这个家伙在这儿
Why is he here?
他只是作家  不是警察
He's a writer, not a cop.
回答问题  格雷格  你是否和苏菲上过床
Answer the question, Greg. Did you ever sleep with Sophie?
一两次而已
Once or twice.
但那是在凯拉和我相识之前
But it was before Kyra and I even met,
而且我和苏菲都知道彼此不适合
and we both knew that it was a mistake.
不适合苏菲还要再找你
A mistake that Sophie tried to repeat.
可能她得手了
Or maybe she succeeded.
没有  当我看到她  我吓坏了
No. When I saw her, I freaked.
我用力推开她  她摔在了地板上
I shoved her away. She fell on the floor.
她的耳环肯定是因为那样才掉的
That must have been when her earring came off.
我还没反应过来  她就出去了
Before I could do anything else, she ran out the door.
这一切发生得太快
I mean it all happened so fast, it didn't...
感觉像是做梦似的
it didn't even seem like it was real.
在你知道苏菲被杀的时候
Why didn't you say anything
为什么要知情不报
when you found out that Sophie was murdered?
我就是怕引起误会
Because I knew how it would sound.
像现在这样的误会吗  真是谎话连篇
Pretty much like it sounds right now, like a lie.
我受够了  我要他离开
Okay, that's it. I want him gone.
很明显他是冲着我来的
He's clearly got it out for me
因为他想和我未婚妻重修旧好
cause he wants to get back in my fiance's pants.
我可不是杀人案的嫌疑犯
I'm not the murder suspect here.
他离开前我不会开口了
I am done answering questions until he is gone.
这儿轮不到你下命令  格雷格
You don't make demands here, Greg.
卡塞尔
Castle.
去看看莱恩和埃斯波西托回来了没
Go and see if Ryan and Esposito have come back
看看法证在格雷格的房间有没有发现
with the forensics from Greg's hotel room.
我们再来整理一下整个过程
Now walk me through what happened again.
别担心  格雷格
Hey, don't you worry about this, Greg.
我会善后的
I got your back covered.
谢谢  泰迪叔叔
Thanks, Uncle Teddy.
真不敢相信你就这么放他走了
Can't believe you're letting him just walk out of here.
我没有足够证据起诉他
Yeah, well, I don't have enough evidence to convict him.
别告诉我你相信他说的
Oh, don't tell me you believe that story.
那简单就是一部糟透了的成人电影
It's like a porn movie gone wrong.
的确  但如果是你要编故事骗人
Exactly, and if you were gonna make up a story,
你会编个这么糟的吗
would you make up something like that?
那又怎样  只能证明他不会编
So? The guy is a suit, not a storyteller.
并不代表他没做
It doesn't make him any less guilty.
别误会  他的嫌疑依然最重
Look, don't get me wrong. He's still our best suspect.
不像你  我只是还没准备好起诉他谋杀
I'm just not as ready to convict him of murder as you seem to be.
所以你就把我踢出了审讯室
Is that why you kicked me out of the interrogation?
很明显我单独审问效果更好
It was clear that I was gonna get more out of Greg alone.
你已经让感情蒙蔽了眼睛
You're just too close to this case to see that.
你是指我和凯拉太亲近
You mean I'm too close to her.
不错  知道我为什么这么觉得吗
Yes, and do you know how I know that?
往常的你这时候早已遍寻各种可能性
If you weren't, you'd be all over the possibility
去证明凯拉谋杀了苏菲
that Kyra could've killed Sophie.
完全没可能
That's impossible.
理查德·卡塞尔是不会说这句话的
See, that's not what Richard Castle would say.
他会想像婚礼的前一晚
He would paint a picture about the night before the wedding,
凯拉有可能睡不着
about how Kyra couldn't fall asleep,
于是她下楼去找格雷格
and so she went down to see Greg.
没想到苏菲从房间走出来
Only to find Sophie emerging from his room,
凯拉觉得未婚夫背叛了她
and the thought that her fiance could cheat on her
而且是在婚礼前夜  这太过份了
the night before their wedding was too much.
于是她尾随苏菲回房并与其对质
And so she follows Sophie to her room and confronts her.
暴力发生  苏菲陨命
And when things get violent, Sophie ends up dead.
你必须离凯拉远远的  卡塞尔
You have to stay away from her, Castle.
直到结案为止
Until this case is closed.
理查德·卡塞尔  你知不知道自己在做什么
Richard Castle, what the hell are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
她是别人的新娘
She's getting married to another man.
只是张照片而已
It's just a picture.
无异于玩火自焚
No, it's a loaded gun.
我是卡塞尔
Castle.
所有人的婚礼都是这个样子吗
Is everybody's wedding like this?
凯拉
Kyra.
我的伴娘被人杀了
So my bridesmaid's dead.
未婚夫可能是凶手
Uh, my fiance might be a murderer,
然后你又出现在我面前
and then there's you.
你只是受的打击太大了
You've just been through a bad shock. That's all.
你能和我见个面吗
Will you come meet me somewhere?
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think that'd be a good idea.
求你了
Please.
我只是想离开酒店一会儿
I just need to get out of the hotel for a little while.
如果继续听我妈在这里絮叨
I-if I have to listen to my mother judge me anymore,
恐怕我要抓几个人质了
I might start taking hostages.
感同身受
I understand completely.
屋顶见面怎样
How about the roof?
我们的秘密屋顶
Our secret roof.
太好了
That's perfect.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的天
Oh, brother.
我希望你明白自己在做什么
I hope you know what you're doing, kiddo.
是的
Yeah...
我也想明白
Me, too.
你怎么会知道门没锁
How did you know the door would still be unlocked
毕竟这么多年了
after all these years?
有些事是不会变的
Some things never change.
那年夏天我们总是待在这儿
We spent so much time up here that summer.
我下课后你就会来
You would come over after I got out of class.
一手拎着吃的  一手拿着笔记本
Bag of food in one hand, and that notebook in the other.
接着我开始写作  你假装学习
And then I would write, and you would pretend to study.
-我才没假装呢  -是吗
- I wasn't pretending. - Oh?
好吧  你太有魅力了让我无法抗拒
Okay, well, I just had a hard time keeping my hands off of you.
格雷格知道你在这儿吗
Does Greg know you're here?
他跟我讲了苏菲去过他房间
He told me about Sophie in his room
还有他和苏菲以前的关系
and about, uh, him and Sophie... before.
他说很抱歉之前没有告诉我
He said he was sorry he didn't tell me.
那你信任他吗
Do you believe him?
我只是不想看到你受伤害
I just don't want to see you get hurt.
太迟了
Hmm. Too late.
我想你  里克
I missed you, Rick.
重逢前我可不知道有这么想你
And I didn't realize how much until I saw you yesterday.
我也想你
I missed you, too.
我跟你说过什么
What did I tell you?
什么
What?
我到底是说清楚了还是没有
Did I or did I not make myself clear?
说清楚了
Yes.
那你知不知道  知晓你的作为我有多烦
Do you know how much it annoys me, knowing what you doing.
碰你不该碰的
Touching things that should be touched,
动你不该动的
yanking on things that shouldn't be yanked?
没有人动任何的东西
No one--no, no, body yanked on anything.
真得吗  那这个你如何解释
Really? Then how do you explain this?
什么
Huh?
别这样看着我
Oh, don't give me that look.
我告诫过你无数次了  别动我的椅子
I've told you a million times not to mess with my chair.
没错  不碰
Right. No.
对不起
I'm sorry.
再也不会发生这种事了
And it-- it won't happen again.
昨晚我和她见面了
I saw her last night.
我知道
I know.
什么
What?
你监视我吗
You had me under surveillance?
不是你  而是凯拉
Not you. Kyra.
为什么要监视凯拉
Why would you have Kyra under surveillance?
因为她是谋杀案的嫌犯
She's a murder suspect.
不  苏菲遇害
Oh, no, no, see, Sophie's murder
是一个完全独立的  非预谋性案件
was an isolated crime of passion.
监视凯拉
Watching Kyra after the fact
是浪费警力
would be a waste of police resources,
而你不该这么做
which we both know you would not do.
我没法保证你不做傻事
I had to make sure that you didn'to anything stupid,
而你竟然真那么做了
which you did.
我们只是接了个吻  仅此而已
We just kissed. That's all that happened.
现在仅此而已
That's all that happened for now.
财务...
Hey, the financial...
你们还好吧
Everything okay?
-没事  -不好
- Yeah. - No.
好
Okay.
新郎的财务状况  没有可疑
Financials came in on our groom. No red flags.
不过对于有信托基金的人来说
He actually lives pretty modest
他倒是过的很节俭
for someone with a trust fund.
实验室有消息吗
Anything back from the lab?
没有有用的结果
Nothing useful.
格雷格的头发和纤维样本并不吻合
Greg's hair and fiber samples came back negative.
除了耳环  没有其他物证
Other than the earring, there's no physical evidence
证明他是凶手
tying him to the murder.
所以我重新检查了苏菲参加婚礼的行程
So I retraced Sophie's steps leading up to the wedding.
她周五入住博蒙特酒店
She checked into the Beaumont on Friday,
但周四上午已抵达纽约
but she flew in to the city on Thursday morning.
周四一整天她在做什么呢
What was she doing all day Thursday?
不知道  我也是预演晚宴才见到她
I don't know. I didn't even see her until the rehearsal dinner,
我们一句话也没说
and we didn't even talk.
恐怕我帮不上忙  我跟她不熟
I'm afraid I can't help you. I, uh, I barely knew the girl.
不  我第一次见到苏菲
No, the first time I saw Sophie
是在周五早上的婚礼早餐
was at the wedding breakfast on Friday morning.
我不知道苏菲在做什么
I have no idea what Sophie was doing,
但肯定没好事
but I'm sure it was nothing good.
你们知道吗
Did you know
她在订婚派对后给我打电话
that she called me after the engagement party
叫我给她付机票钱
to ask me to pay for her flight?
-你付钱了吗  -当然没有
- And did you? - Of course not.
我告诉她  自己的事自己做
I told her, people have to make their own way.
所以你不知道苏菲周四在做什么吗
So you have no idea what Sophie did on Thursday?
不知道  但猜猜我周五刚见到她时
No. But guess what she was doing on Friday
她在做什么
when I first saw her.
What's that?
在酒店的商场购物
Shopping at the hotel store.
她跟所有人说她一贫如洗
Here she is telling everybody how broke she is,
然后摇身一变  挥金如土
And somehow... oh, suddenly, she has money to burn.
买鞋  买礼服  住宿费和机票
Between the shoes, the dress, the hotel and the flight,
这周末苏菲轻轻松松花掉了三千美元
Sophie must have dropped 3 grand on this weekend, easy.
让人费解  她在银行的余额只有18美元
I don't know how. Her bank balance is $18
信用卡也已刷爆
And her credit cards are maxed out.
毒贩说她买迷药花了多少钱
How much did the drug dealer say she paid for the roofies?
两百现金
200 bucks cash.
问题是
The problem is,
为买飞纽约的机票  她取出最后一百块
Sophie withdrew her last $100 to fly to New York.
我认为  她应该拿不出两百块
As far as I can tell, she didn't have the 200 bucks to give.
那么是谁为迷药买了单
So who paid for the drugs?
别提迷药了  我当过六次伴娘了
Forget the drugs. I've been a bridesmaid six times.
她怎么买得起礼服
How did she pay for the dress?
好  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
苏菲不仅用现金付了机票
So not only did Sophie pay for her flight in cash,
还用现金缴了之前三个月的房租
but she also made her last three rent payments in cash as well.
知不知道这些钱从哪里来的
Any idea where it all came from?
还不知道
Not yet.
当了六次伴娘
So... six times a bridesmaid, huh?
你没有照片  对吗
You wouldn't happen to have any pictures, would you?
谁想看新娘用品店的监控录像
Who feels like watching a little bridal shop surveillance video?
好看吗  有什么劲爆内容吗
Is it good? Will--will I be shocked?
你绝对想不到的
Oh, you definitely did not see this one coming.
这是苏菲
Okay, there's Sophie.
格雷格的叔叔泰迪
Greg's uncle Teddy.
他说自己和她不熟
He said he barely knew her.
他绝对认识她
Oh, he definitely knew her.
根据新娘用品店老板的话
According to the bridal shop owner,
当泰迪为礼服买单时  苏菲说
when Teddy was paying for the dress, Sophie told him
不知道自己能不能做好
she wasn't sure if she could go through with it.
但泰迪说  他已经为她做了那么多
But Teddy said, after all he'd done for her,
她不能再退缩了
she couldn't back out now.
听过新娘的婚前恐惧症  不想伴娘也有
Now I've heard of brides getting cold feet. But bridesmaids?
他是用现金买的礼服吗
Did he pay for the dress in cash?
是  你怎么知道
Yep. How'd you know?
好叔叔用现金付账
All that cash means that uncle sugar daddy didn't want
就掩盖了他和苏菲的关系
a paper trail tying him to whatever Sophie was doing for him.
他们之间会是什么关系呢
Yeah, but what could it be?
为什么苏菲一定要参加格雷格的婚礼呢
And why was it so important for Sophie to go to Greg's wedding?
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
你们没有证据起诉我
You don't have enough to build a case against me,
就抓我的家人吗
So you go after someone else in my family?
我们只为找出真相
We're trying to get to the truth.
审我叔叔就行了吗
By hauling in my uncle?
天啊  他几乎不认识苏菲
For god sakes, he barely knew Sophie.
但他为她700美元的礼服买单
And yet he paid for her $700 dress
还有她来这里的飞机票
and her plane ticket out here.
他给她买礼服
He bought her dress?
如果跟她不熟  为什么这么做
If he barely knew her, why would he do that?
有传言说
We heard through the grapevine
苏菲可能没钱
that Sophie might have some trouble making the money
来参加婚礼
to come out here to the wedding.
泰迪可能是为了我们才帮她
Maybe Teddy was trying to help her out for us.
这并不能解释清楚
That doesn't explain the $1,500
为何三个月给了她1500美元
that he paid her the last three month.
他给她钱
He was-- he was paying her?
为什么
For what?
他们做了个交易
Some kind of deal they got going on.
我们认为这可能
We think it could have something to do
和她在你婚礼前夜的行为有关
with the way she was behaving the night before your wedding.
没错
Yeah, sure.
他花钱让苏菲迷倒一个伴郎
Uh, he--he paid Sophie to roofie a groomsman
然后爬到我的床上
and then to climb into bed with me.
我知道这听起来
Look, we know how this sounds--
听起来就像里克小册子里的情节
It sounds like something out of one of Rick's little books.
小册子
Little books?
除了搅乱婚礼
What would even be the point of that
还能有什么目的
except to mess up the wedding?
泰迪为什么要这么做
Why the hell would Teddy want that?
我们也想知道
That's what we're trying to find out.
天啊  接下来你就会告诉我
Oh, my god. For god sakes. Next you're gonna tell me
他也爱上凯拉了
that he's in love with Kyra, too.
什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你们俩
You guys--
你知道我是什么意思
You know damn well what it's supposed to mean.
不  格雷格  我不知道
No Greg, I don't.
如果你有话想说
If you've got something to say to me,
直说好了
why don't you just say it?
我爱凯拉  里克  她是我的一切
I love Kyra, Rick. She means the world to me.
也许你不懂  也许你无所谓
Maybe you can't see it. Maybe you don't care.
但泰迪只会支持我们
But Teddy has been nothing but supportive of us
全心全意
the whole way.
他提交我们的婚礼申请
He filed our wedding license.
他帮我们起草婚前协议
He helped us write our prenup.
他一直照看
He always looks after...
什么
What?
我打个电话
I gotta make a call.
你们知道我坐这多久了吗
Do you know how long I've been sitting in here?
不好意思让你等  我还没吃饭
I'm sorry for the wait. I hadn't had anything to eat.
我们没讨论好去哪个餐馆
We couldn't decide on a restaurant.
很好笑吗
What do you think this is, funny?
这些文件眼熟吗  墨菲先生
Do you recognize these files, Mr. Murphy?
你们去了我的办公室
You went to my office?
有搜查令的  不用担心
We got a warrant first. Don't worry.
你这种外行根本理解不了
Look, a layman like you couldn't possibly understand
格雷格家产业在经济和法律上的
the financial and the legal complications
复杂性
of an estate like Greg's.
我想他只是骂你蠢
I think he just called you stupid.
格雷格的祖父母建立了一份信托基金
Greg's grandparents established a trust fund
他本将在婚礼当天得到
that he was going to receive on his wedding day,
而你是遗嘱执行人  我怎么知道的
and named you executor. How am I doing so far?
过去的五年间
And for the past five years,
你一直从那笔基金中窃取款项
you have been stealing from that fund
以满足你奢侈的生活
to fuel your expensive lifestyle--
在汉普顿买了间房  还买了一辆法拉利
a house in the hamptons, a Ferrari.
最昂贵的隆胸手术
A pair of top-of-the-line breast implants.
我想你应该不是自用
I'm assuming those aren't for you, though.
我的私生活与你们无关
My personal life is none of your business.
除非这跟杀人案有关
It is when it leads to a murder.
你在股市赔了一大笔钱
You lost a ton of money in the market.
大家都赔了
Everybody did.
但只有你能接触格雷格的信托基金
But not everybody had access to Greg's trust fund.
你花光了自己的钱  就开始用他的
When you ran out of your own money, you started using his.
两百万美金几乎挥霍一空
Burned through almost the entire $2 million,
然后他告诉你
and then when he called you
他要订婚了  你慌了
to tell you he was getting engaged, you panicked
因为你补不上这个大洞了
because you didn't have enough equity to put it back.
你想到阻止事情败露的唯一方法
You realized the only way to avoid detection
就是阻止婚礼  但是怎么做呢
was to put a stop to the wedding, but how?
格雷格很明显爱着凯拉
Greg was clearly in love with Kyra.
凯拉也爱他
Kyra was in love with him.
然后你在订婚派对见到苏菲
And then you met Sophie at the engagement party,
想到拿她做破坏格雷格婚礼的
and you realized that she was the perfect instrument
完美棋子
to sabotage Greg's wedding
因为她非常需要钱
because she was so desperate for money.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
尤其因为她还单恋着格雷格
The fact that she still carried a torch for Greg
说服她午夜无人时
made it that much easier to convince her
溜进格雷格的房间就更容易了
to sneak into Greg's room in the middle of the night...
这个  苏菲的相机
With this- Sophie's video camera.
你放在酒店的行李里的
We found this in your luggage in the hotel.
上面还有苏菲的指纹
It still has Sophie's fingerprints all over it.
她没有完成你的要求  对不对
Only she didn't quite get the footage you were hoping for, did she?
格雷格拒绝苏菲后
When Greg refused Sophie's advances,
她就改变主意了
she had a change of heart.
她跑回房间  你正在那里等她
She ran back to her room, where you were there, waiting for her.
发生了什么  墨菲先生
What happened, Mr. Murphy?
她是否威胁说要把你供出来
Did she threaten to expose you,
告诉大家你指使她破坏婚礼
tell everybody what you asked her to do?
你可不能让事情这么发展下去
You couldn't let that happen.
然后你想到还有一种方法
And then you realized there was another way
能破坏格雷格的婚礼  杀死伴娘
to sabotage Greg's wedding-- kill a bridesmaid.
精彩绝伦的好故事
Wow. What a story.
而且讲得绘声绘色
And very well told, I might add.
但也不过是瞎掰
Yeah, but that's all it is... a story.
真的吗
Really?
你还记得我说过
Do you remember how I told you
我们搜查了你的行李吗
that we went through your luggage?
我们发现了这个领带夹
We found this tie tack.
白金的  对吗
Platinum, right?
我们在苏菲背部的伤口上
Did you know that we found trace evidence of platinum
发现了微量的白金
in the wounds in Sophie's back?
你大概是想不到的
You probably didn't even realize you were making them
你从背后勒死她的时候留下了痕迹
when you were choking her from behind.
所以你完全没想到
Which is why it never occurred to you
要丢掉这个能将你绳之于法的
to get rid of the one piece of physical evidence
物证
that tied you to the crime.
不好意思让你久等了
We're sorry we kept you waiting.
苏菲  你要做什么
Sophie, what are you doing?
来啊  格雷格  你和我最后一次
Come on, Greg. You and me, one last time.
我们以前就很和谐
We were good together.
-不  住手  -来嘛  会很爽的
- No. Stop it. - Come on. It'll be fun.
不  你怎么了
No. What's the matter with you?
-我只是想  -我明天要结婚了
- I just thought-- - I'm getting married tomorrow, okay,
和我爱的女人
to the woman that I love.
泰迪的计划本可能成功德
Teddy's plan would've worked, too,
只是他忽略了一个人
If it weren't for the one thing he didn't count on.
格雷格
Greg.
他是个好男人  凯拉
He's a good man, Kyra.
一个守信的男人
He's an honorable man.
深爱着你
And he loves you.
我知道
I know.
我也爱他
And I love him, too.
可这并不表示
But that does not mean
我会时不时想念你
that I'm not gonna think about you from time to time.
最好是
Oh, you better.
纽约城那么多场婚礼
Of all the murders
那么多谋杀案
in all the cities at all the weddings...
你却来帮了我
and you walk into mine.
很高兴我来了
I'm glad I did.
谢谢你  里克
Thank you, Rick.
把他完全交给你了
He's all yours.
如果有谁要反对
If any person can show just cause
这两位新人的结合
as to why these two may not be joined together,
请示意  否则请永远祝福他们
Let them speak now or forever hold their peace.
以纽约州法律赋予的合法权利
By the power vested in me by the state of New York
我现在宣布你们正式成为合法夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以亲吻你的妻子了
You may kiss the bride.